

604-616-8765 • linkedin.com/in/bernard-yang • bernardyang@outlook.com • LIC-2023-0043591-R01

PROFILE

A <u>Level 2 General Insurance Salesperson</u> with 3 years experience in the insurance industry. A dedicated team player who is also resourceful and constantly thinking of unique ways to assist both customers and team members. Currently working in a position assisting producers with a book of business primarily in personal lines. Seeking a position with a company that is readily adapting to the technological changes in this industry.

EXPERIENCE

Customer Service Representative

Insureline Brokers

May 2023 - Present Vancouver, BC

- Utilize computer programming knowledge to prefill 100's of questionnaires, disclosures, LOBs saving time for team members and producers
- Process PolicyCentre renewals, out-of-province transfers, and all other incidental ICBC transactions including Family Private Auto
- Help producers get quotes via Applied Rating System, look up wording, get binding through underwriters, get quotes for hard to place policies through special market
- Use Applied Epic to enter activities, endorsements, cancellations, invoice payments, create policy shells, create CSIO applications

Real Estate Agent

Macdonald Realty

July 2018 - July 2020

Vancouver, BC

- Attended agents' open house and analyzed sales data on MLS to accurately perform comparative market analysis
- · Prepared all documents pertaining to contract of purchase and sale, and listing agreements

Customer Service Representative

Tony Lau Insurance

June 2015 - Jan 2018

Vancouver, BC

- · Helped in-house, walk-in clients, producers with home, travel, and ICBC insurance
- Experience working with Applied TAM and PowerQuote

EDUCATION

Diploma in Web Development

Lighthouse Labs

May 2021 - Aug 2021

Remote, BC

2009 - 2011

Richmond, BC

Kwantlen Polytechnic University

Diploma in Business Administration

INSURANCE TOOLKIT

- Applied Epic, Applied Rating System, Applied TAM, PowerQuote
- Insurance Markets: Aviva, Family, Gore Mutual, Intact, Optimum West, Wawanesa

SKILLS

- Intermediate knowledge of Microsoft Excel, and Outlook
- · Working knowledge of computer programming languages including Python, JavaScript, SQL
- Cantonese conversant